A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller papers, Office and Home Files FA1353
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Personal Papers and Interests, 1888-2010; 1; 118.83 Cubic Feet 281 containers.
  - Memorials, 1956-2009; 1_7
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Music - "America the Beautiful", 2004 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Music - "Now the Day is Over", 2004 (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Music - "O Love that Wilt Not Let Me Go", 2004 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Music - "On a Clear Day", 2004 (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Music - "Stardust", 2004 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Music - Barbara Streisand, 2004 (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Music - "When the Saints Go Marching In", 2004 (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Music - "When You're Smiling", 2004 (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Invitee Lists, 2004 September (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Obituaries - New York Times (Reprint), 2004 July 12 (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - LSR - Family and Friends - Memorials and Sympathy (Box 138, Folder 9)
    - LSR - Memorial - Gifts, 2004-2006 (Box 139, Folder 13)
    - LSR - Obituaries and Memorials, 2005-2008 (Box 167, Folder 12)
    - MFR - "The Alphabet of MFR" - Tribute Photo Album from Family, 1997 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - MSKCC - Memorial Tribute to LSR at MSKCC, 2004 September 27 (Box 191, Folder 4)
    - MSKCC - Memorial Tribute to LSR, 2004 September 27 (Box 251, Folder 3)
    - LSR Memorial Service at Riverside Church - Guestbooks, 2004 September 9 (Box 192, Folder 1-4, Box 193, Folder 1-2)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - NAR, 1979 (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Memorial Services - Family and Friends, 1960s-1990s (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - LSR - MFR - Sympathy Letters - A-G, 1997 (Box 283, Folder 5-6)
    - LSR - MFR - Sympathy Letters - A-D, 1997 (Box 284, Folder 1-4)
    - LSR - MFR - Sympathy Letters - E-J, 1997 (Box 285, Folder 1-6)
    - LSR - MFR - Sympathy Letters - H-L, 1997 (Box 286, Folder 1)
    - LSR - MFR - Sympathy Letters - K-M, 1997 (Box 286, Folder 2-4)
    - LSR - MFR - Sympathy Letters - M-Q, 1997 (Box 287, Folder 1-4)
    - LSR - MFR - Sympathy Letters - R, 1997 (Box 287, Folder 5)
    - LSR - MFR - Sympathy Letters - R-T, 1997 (Box 288, Folder 1-4)
    - LSR - MFR - Sympathy Letters - U-Z, 1997 (Box 289, Folder 1-4)
    - MFR - Obituaries, 1997 (Box 289, Folder 5)
    - MFR - Memorial Service - Guest Books, 1997 May 14 (Box 289, Folder 6-7, Box 290, Folder 1-2)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Riverside Church - Booklets, 2004 September 9 (Box 333, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Obituaries - Various, 2004 (Box 334, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Obituaries - Fraser Seitel - Clippings, 2004 (Box 334, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Obituaries - Vermont Standard, 2004 (Box 334, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Obituaries - St. John's "Trade Winds" News, 2004 (Box 334, Folder 4)
    - LSR - Obituaries - New York Times, 2004 (Box 334, Folder 5)
    - LSR - Tribute to JDR Jr, 1956-1961 (Box 339, Folder 4)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - Condolence Letter List, 2004 (Box 391, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - Condolence Letters to David Rockefeller, 2004 (Box 391, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - Tributes to LSR, 2004 (Box 391, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - MSKCC Tribute, 2004 September 27 (Box 391, Folder 4, Box 392, Folder 5)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - Jackson Lake Lodge Memorial, 2004 September 15 (Box 391, Folder 5)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - Upaya Zen Center Memorial Service, 2004 July 14 (Box 391, Folder 6)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - Statements, 2004 (Box 391, Folder 7)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - New York Times Statement, 2004 July 16-19 (Box 391, Folder 8)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - Letter from "New Yorkers for Parks" to the New York Times, 2004 (Box 391, Folder 9)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - Notice 845 Fifth Avenue Corporation, 2004 July 13 (Box 391, Folder 10)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - Miscellaneous Notices, 2004 (Box 391, Folder 11)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - Office Statements, 2004 July 13 (Box 391, Folder 12)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - Original Condolence Letters, 2004 (Box 391, Folder 13-14, Box 392, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - Messages, 2004 July 12 (Box 392, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - Responses - Letters of Appreciation, 2004 (Box 392, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - Princeton "One with Accord", 2004 Fall (Box 392, Folder 4)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - Acknowledgement Card, 2004 (Box 392, Folder 6)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - Contributions - MSKCC and Woodstock, 2004 (Box 392, Folder 7)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - Flowers, 2004 (Box 392, Folder 8)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - Guestbooks, 2004 (Box 392, Folder 9)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - Memorial Service, 2004 July 16 (Box 392, Folder 10)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - Memorial Contributions, 2004 (Box 392, Folder 11)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - Steven C. Rockefeller's Prayer for LSR, 2004 July 16 (Box 392, Folder 12)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - Invitation to Memorial Service, 2004 (Box 392, Folder 13)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - Acceptances-Declinations, 2004 (Box 392, Folder 14)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - Memorial Service Planning, 2004 (Box 392, Folder 15)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - Reception - Catering, 2004 (Box 392, Folder 16)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - Flowers, 2004 (Box 392, Folder 17)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - Music, 2004 (Box 392, Folder 18)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - Program, 2004 (Box 392, Folder 19)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - Speakers, 2004 (Box 392, Folder 20)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - David Rockefeller Eulogy, 2004 (Box 392, Folder 21)
    - LSR - Memorial Service Files - Guest Book and Signatures, 2004 (Box 392, Folder 22)
    - Lucy Waletzky - Butterfly Garden for LSR, 2000 May (Box 393, Folder 1)
  - Personal Property and Residence Files, 1920-2009; 1_8
    - Pamphlets and Brochures - New York and Pocantico, 1959-2000s (Box 80, Folder 1-3)
    - LSR Residence - New York - 834 Fifth Avenue, 1988-2004 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - LSR Residence - Wyoming - JY Ranch, 1987-1994 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Property - Wyoming - JY Ranch - Managers, 1996-2005 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - LSR Residence - Wyoming - Valley Ranch, 1982-1994 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - LSR Residence - Woodstock - Echo Acre, 1998 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Tribute to T. M. Debevoise, 1995 February 7 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - 834 Fifth Avenue Apartment, 1946-1979 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - 834 Fifth Avenue Apartment - Clayton W. Frye File, 1946-2004 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Woodstock - Mansion - Wine Cellar, 1959 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - LSR - Sotheby's Appraisal of 5600 Art, 2004 August 22 (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - LSR - Sotheby's - JY Ranch and Rockefeller Office Items, 2005 April 7 (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - LSR - Sotheby's - Property Schedule, 2005 (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - Appraisals - 834 5th Avenue (Chait Galleries), 2004 December 6 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Appraisals - Kent House (Chait Galleries), 2004 December 6 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Appraisals - JY Ranch Personal Property (SH Enterprises), 2004 November 22 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - LSR - Rolodex - 834 Fifth Avenue (Box 135)
    - LSR - Rolodex - 834 Fifth Avenue (Box 136)
    - MFR - Rolodex - 834 Fifth Avenue (Box 136)
    - 834 Fifth Avenue - Book of Recipes (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - LSR - Miscellaneous Files from Room 5600 (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - LSR-MFR - Personal Rolodex (Box 161)
    - LSR-MFR - Inscribed Books from Kent House and 834 Fifth Avenue Libraries - Distribution, 2009 (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - LSR - List of LSR Legal Files from Patterson Belknap, 2006 (Box 166, Folder 13)
    - LSR - 834 Fifth Avenue - Chronological File, 1996-2000 (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - LSR - 834 Fifth Avenue - Chronological File, 2001-2002 (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - LSR - 834 Fifth Avenue - Chronological File, 2003 (Box 178, Folder 3-4)
    - LSR - 834 Fifth Avenue - Chronological Fie, 2004 (Box 178, Folder 5, Box 179, Folder 1-2)
    - Ruth Haupert - 834 Fifth Avenue - Chronological File, 2004 (Box 179, Folder 3-4)
    - Ruth Haupert - 834 Fifth Avenue - Chronological File, 2005 (Box 166, Folder 14-15)
    - LSR - Rolodex, 2005 (Box 183)
    - LSR - 834 Fifth Avenue - Library - Assorted Books with Inscriptions or Bookplates (Box 233, Box 234, Box 235)
    - LSR - 834 Fifth Avenue - Library - Assorted Books with Inscriptions or Bookplates (Box 237, Box 238)
    - LSR - 834 Fifth Avenue - Library - Assorted Books with Inscriptions (Box 259, Folder 3, Box 260, Folder 1)
    - LSR - 834 Fifth Avenue - Library - Aviation - Eastern Airlines Airplane Model (Box 236)
    - LSR - 834 Fifth Avenue - Library - Aviation - Books (Box 239, Box 240, Box 241)
    - LSR - 834 Fifth Avenue - Library - Aviation - Books (Box 258, Box 259, Folder 1)
    - LSR - 834 Fifth Avenue - Library - Aviation Materials (Box 259, Folder 2)
    - LSR - 834 Fifth Avenue - Library - Conservation and Environment - Books (Box 261, Folder 3, Box 262, Box 263, Box 264)
    - LSR - Kent House - Library - Conservation and the Environment - Publications and Reports (Box 265, Folder 1-3, Box 267, Folder 4)
    - LSR - 834 Fifth Avenue - Library - Holy Bible (Revised Standard Edition) - Given to LSR by JDR Jr, 1955 (Box 226, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Kent House - Library - Personal and Professional Interests - Books, Pamphlets and Reports (Box 260, Folder 2-3)
    - LSR - Kent House - Library - Personal and Professional Interests - Articles, Pamphlets and Reports (Box 261, Folder 1-2)
    - LSR - Kent House - Library - Personal and Professional Interests - Articles, Pamphlets and Reports (Box 266, Folder 1-3, Box 267)
    - MFR - 834 Fifth Avenue - Library - Faith - Books and Pamphlets (Box 291, Folder 4, Box 292, Box 293)
    - MFR - 834 Fifth Avenue - Library - YWCA - Books and Reports (Box 294, Box 295, Box 296)
    - MFR - 834 Fifth Avenue - Library - YWCA - Publications, 1950s-1960s (Box 297)
    - LSR - 834 Fifth Avenue - Library - Assorted Books and Periodicals (Box 298)
    - LSR - 834 Fifth Avenue - Library - Assorted Books (Box 299, Box 300)
    - LSR - Miscellaneous, 1960s (Box 251, Folder 2)
    - LSR - General Files, 1979-2003 (Box 267, Folder 5, Box 268, Folder 1-3)
    - LSR - Health and Medicine, 1989-1997 (Box 268, Folder 4)
    - LSR - General Files, 1990s-2000s (Box 273, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Pamphlets and Reports - General, 1960s-2000s (Box 273, Folder 2-3)
    - LSR - Pamphlets and Reports - Art, 1990s-2000s (Box 273, Folder 4)
    - LSR - Conservation and Environment, 1970s-2002 (Box 274, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Pamphlets and Reports - Conservation and Environment, 1960s (Box 274, Folder 2-3)
    - LSR - Aviation - Eastern Airlines - Flag with Eastern Airlines (EAL) Insignia (Box 274, Folder 4)
    - LSR - Aviation - Eastern Airlines - Photos and Postcards (Box 275, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Aviation - Eastern Airlines - "Too Low They Build, Who Build Beneath the Stars", 1967 (Box 275, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Aviation - Eastern Airlines - Banshee Ash Tray (Box 275, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Aviation - Eastern Airlines - Playing Cards (Box 276, Folder 1)
      2 decks
    - LSR - Aviation - Eastern Airlines, 1940s-1980s (Box 276, Folder 2-3)
    - LSR - Aviation - Eastern Airlines - Duck Hawk Sculpture, 2004 (Box 276, Folder 4)
    - LSR - Eastern Airlines Merger, 1979 (Box 412, Folder 5)
    - LSR - "Miami Millions" (Box 277)
      Restricted - Preservation concerns
    - LSR - Clippings and Periodicals, 1930s-1970s (Box 282, Folder 1-2)
    - LSR - Kent House - Calendars, 1920s (Box 282, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Miscellaneous Cards and Letters to LSR, 1973-1978 (Box 282, Folder 4-5)
    - LSR - Miscellaneous Cards and Letters to LSR, 1979-1986 (Box 283, Folder 1-2)
    - LSR - Notable Letters to LSR, 1984-1988 (Box 283, Folder 3)
    - 834 Fifth Avenue - Apartment Files - Photographs, undated (Box 303, Folder 4)
    - 834 Fifth Avenue - Apartment Files - Renovation, 1949-2003 (Box 304, Folder 1)
    - 834 Fifth Avenue - Apartment Files - Fire, 1994 (Box 304, Folder 2)
    - 834 Fifth Avenue - Apartment Files - 834 Work - Phase I, 1988 Summer (Box 304, Folder 3)
    - 834 Fifth Avenue - Apartment Files - 834 Work - Phase II, 1988 Summer (Box 304, Folder 4-5)
    - 834 Fifth Avenue - Apartment Files - 834 Work - Phase III, 1988 Summer (Box 305, Folder 1-2)
    - 834 Fifth Avenue - Apartment Files - Elevator, 1991 (Box 305, Folder 3)
    - 834 Fifth Avenue - Apartment Files - MFR Sitting Room - Disaster, 2000 (Box 305, Folder 4)
    - 834 Fifth Avenue - Apartment Files - Leaks, 1994-1997 (Box 305, Folder 5)
    - 834 Fifth Avenue - Apartment Files - Phase IV, 1991-1992 (Box 305, Folder 6)
    - 834 Fifth Avenue - Apartment Files - Carpet Beetles, 1999 (Box 305, Folder 7)
    - 834 Fifth Avenue - Apartment Files - Kent House Refurbishing (Tarrytown) - Theodor Muller, 1990 (Box 305, Folder 8)
    - 834 Fifth Avenue - Apartment Files - Events at 834 - Nichols Christmas Party, 1995 December 13 (Box 306, Folder 1)
    - 834 Fifth Avenue - Apartment Files - Events at 834 - Historic Hudson Event, 1997 (Box 306, Folder 2)
    - 834 Fifth Avenue - Apartment Files - Events at 834 - Lucy Waletzky Party - Book Signing, 1999 April 7 (Box 306, Folder 3)
    - 834 Fifth Avenue - Apartment Files - Events at 834 - Laura Chasin Event - Public Conversations Project, 1999 April 12 (Box 306, Folder 4)
    - 834 Fifth Avenue - Apartment Files - Events at 834 - Laura Chasin Event - Public Conversations Project, 1998-1999 (Box 306, Folder 5)
    - 834 Fifth Avenue - Apartment Files - Events at 834 - Center for Health and the Global Environment, 2000 April 6 (Box 306, Folder 6)
    - 834 Fifth Avenue - Apartment Files - Events at 834 - Trickle Up Event - Wendy Rockefeller, 2000 April 7 (Box 306, Folder 7)
    - 834 Fifth Avenue - Apartment Files - Events at 834 - "Dinner 21", 2000 November 1 (Box 306, Folder 8)
    - 834 Fifth Avenue - Apartment Files - Events at 834 - Central Park Conservancy Event, 2001 May 16 (Box 306, Folder 9)
    - 834 Fifth Avenue - Apartment Files - Events at 834 - Intergenerational Dialogue - M. Morgan Event, 2001 September 25 (Box 306, Folder 10)
    - 834 Fifth Avenue - Apartment Files - Events - "Refreshments on the Porch" - Echo Acres, 2002 July 13 (Box 306, Folder 11)
    - 834 Fifth Avenue - Apartment Files - Events at 834 - YWCA - World Service Council Meeting, 2002 October 18 (Box 306, Folder 12)
    - 834 Fifth Avenue - Apartment Files - Events at 834 - Laura Chasin Event, 2002 October 21 (Box 307, Folder 1)
    - 834 Fifth Avenue - Apartment Files - Events at 834 - Lucy's Dinner - Commonweal, 2002 November 7 (Box 307, Folder 2)
    - 834 Fifth Avenue - Stationary - MFR Stamp and Engraving Plate (Box 339, Folder 1)
  - General Interests, 1972-2009; 1_9
    - Li, Victor, 2001-2003 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Li, Victor - Li Xing School, 1991-2000 (Box 26, Folder 2, Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Lord, June Harrah, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Manitou Foundation - Note - Re the Conservation Fund, Land Use Assessment, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Manitou Foundation - Master Easement Plan, 1999-2000 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Mueller, Robert, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Samueli Institute - Bibliography of Spiritual Healing, Energy Medicine, and Intentionality Research, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      Research compiled by Cindy Crawford and Wayne Jonas, MD. 94 pages.
    - Smith, Fred - General (Box 54, Folder 3)
      Includes obituary.
    - Smith, Fred - 25 Sutton Place South - Appraisal and Sale (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Smith, Richard Norton - NAR Biography, 2002-2004 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - LSR - UFO - Sturrock Report, 1998-1999 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Templeton Foundation - General, 1998-2000 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Templeton Foundation - Humility Theology Information Center, Board of Advisors Meeting, 1998 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Templeton Prize: 1998 Nomination - Fr. Walter J. Smith (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Upaya - Joan Halifax, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Upaya - Halifax Note, 1995-2000 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Venrock, 1974-1999 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Wayfarer Ketch - General, 1992-1999 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Wayfarer Ketch - Aircraft, 1990-1999 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Weil, Andrew - Center for Integrative Medicine Proposal, 1997 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Weil, Andrew - Meeting with LSR, 1997 October 16 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Winks, Robin - Billings Biography (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Winks, Robin: National Parks Magazine, 1999 May-June (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Woodstock - Norman Williams Public Library - General, 1997-2003 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Wolfe, J. J., 1999-2003 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Chernow, Ron - Titan - Reviews (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Boyer, Allston, 1972 May 17 (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Kykuit Tour Pamphlets (Box 167, Folder 11)
    - LSR - Pulsifer, Lynn O., 2009 (Box 167, Folder 13)
    - LSR - Conversation with Dr. Paul Marks, 2003 December 18 (Box 167, Folder 14)
    - LSR - Christian Ministry in the National Parks Conference, 1976 (Box 167, Folder 15)
    - LSR - The Community Center for the Arts, 2001 (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - LSR Paperweights (Box 181, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Mirror Theatre Company Correspondence, 1984 (Box 407, Folder 5)
    - LSR - Leonard Outhwaite - Report on Population, 1948 April (Box 407, Folder 6, Box 408, Folder 1-2)
  - Audiovisual Material, 1971-2004; 1_10
    - LSR - Speeches - Woodrow Wilson Award Speech, Princeton University - Audio Tapes, 1991 February 16 (Box T1)
      Open for research. Digital access copy currently unavailable. Please see a RAC archivist for further instruction.
    - MSKCC - "For Yourself - A Guide to Breast Self Examination", 1998; VHS (Box T1)
      Open for research. Digital access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
    - MSKCC - Town Meeting with MSKCC President Harold Varmus, 2000 January 18; VHS (Box T1)
    - LSR Awards - Congressional Gold Medal to LSR, 1991 September 27; VHS (Box T1)
      Presentation of the Congressional Gold Medal to LSR.
    - Winks, Robin - On the National Parks, 2002 September 8; VHS, 3 copies (Box T1)
    - "A Child's Christmas in Wales" (Box T1)
      with inscription to LSR and MFR.
    - LSR - Memorial Service, 2004; DVD (Box T1)
    - LSR - Meeting with LSR, Fred Smith, Ellen Pomeroy, Clayton W. Frye, Joan Halifax, Fraser Seitel, Ruth Fowler, 2 cassette tapes (Box T1)
    - NAR Interview - Unedited Footage for Africa Art Film, 1977; Cassette tape. (Box T1)
    - MSKCC - Memorial Tribute to LSR, 2004 September 27; 2 dvd (Box T1)
    - LSR - Robert Sikorsky - Media Tour, VHS (Box T1)
    - LSR - The Jackson Hole Story, KUED - Public Television, DVD (Box T1)
    - LSR - The Charlie Rose Show - Paul A. Marks, MD, 1995 May 25; 17 minutes; VHS (Box T1)
    - LSR - Mardy Murie Film Project - "Arctic Dance", 75 minutes; VHS (Box T1)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Center - National Historic Landmark, 1988 September 26; VHS (Box T1)
    - LSR - ACMNF Board Meeting, Yellowstone, 1996 September; VHS (Box T1)
    - LSR - The Woodrow Wilson Award, Princeton University - Lecture, Questions, 1991 February; Cassette tape. (Box T1)
    - Vermont Natural Resources Council - "So Goes Vermont", 1971; 1992; VHS (Box T1)
      Open for research. Digital access copy currently unavaliable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
    - MFR - Memorial Service - Brick Presbyterian Church, NYC, 1997 May 14; VHS; 3 copies (Box T1)
    - MFR - Memorial Service - Brick Presbyterian Church, NYC - Edit 1, 1997 May 14; VHS; 2 copies. (Box T1)
    - MFR - Memorial Service - Brick Presbyterian Church, NYC - Edit 2, 1997 May 14; VHS (Box T1)
    - MFR - YWCA - Week Without Violence Campaign Video, 2 copies.; VHS (Box T1)
    - MFR - YWCA - Week Without Violence - Hillary Rodham Clinton, PSA, 1995 October; VHS (Box T1)
    - LSR - YWCA - Camping Services Campaign Video, 2002; VHS (Box T1)
    - A Service in Celebration of the Life of Mary French Rockefeller, Brick Presbyterian Church, NYC, 1997 May 14; VHS; 7 copies (Box T2)
    - MFR - Memorial - Music from the Service, 1997 May 14; Cassette (Box T2)
    - MFR - Travel - Japan, Hong Kong, Dictet magnetic tape (Box T2)
    - MFR - Travel - India, Burma, Thai, Korea, Dictet magnetic tape (Box T2)
    - MFR - Travel - Philippines, Dictet magnetic tape (Box T2)
    - MFR - Travel - Hawaii, Dictet magnetic tape (Box T2)
    - MFR - Travel - England to Kenya, Dictet magnetic tape (Box T2)
- Art, 1940-2009; 2; 14.57 Cubic Feet 35 containers
  - Mary French Rockefeller (MFR) Estate - Jewelry and Art - Appraisals and Correspondence, 1980-2003 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Mary French Rockefeller (MFR) - Jewelry - Christie's Auction, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Mary French Rockefeller (MFR) - Jewelry - Christie's Auction, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 3-5)
  - LSR and MFR - Appraisals - Sotheby's - New York, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - LSR and MFR - Appraisals - Sotheby's - Kent House, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - LSR and MFR - Appraisals - Sotheby's - Woodstock, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - LSR and MFR - Appraisals - Sotheby's - Wyoming, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - MFR Jewelry - Book I - Photos and Valuations (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - MFR Jewelry - Book II - Photos and Valuations (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - MFR Jewelry - Book III - Photos and Valuations (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - MFR Jewelry - Christie's Photo Album with Family Selections, 1998-2003 (Box 15, Folder 2-3)
  - LSR Properties - Valuations, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 4, Box 16, Folder 1)
  - LSR Properties - Valuations, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 2-3)
  - LSR Properties - Valuations, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 4, Box 17, Folder 1)
  - LSR Properties - Valuations, 1971-1981 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - LSR Properties - JY Indian Basket Collection (Box 17, Folder 3-4)
  - LSR Properties - Valuations, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - MFR Properties - Valuations, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 6-7)
  - LSR Appraisals - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller (AAR) Estate - Japanese Prints and Porcelain (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - LSR Appraisals - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller (AAR) Estate - Inventory, 1940-1967 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - LSR Appraisals - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller (AAR) Estate - LSR Seal Harbor Selections (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - LSR Appraisals - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller (AAR) Estate - Inventories, 1960-1963 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - LSR Appraisals - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller (AAR) Estate - Seal Harbor Sculpture, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - LSR Appraisals - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller (AAR) Estate - Asian and Mediterranean Pictures (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - LSR Appraisals - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller (AAR) Estate - Brass, Fabrics, Earthware (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - LSR Appraisals - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller (AAR) Estate - Rugs (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - LSR Appraisals - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller (AAR) Estate - Religious Figures (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - LSR Appraisals - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller (AAR) Estate - European and American Pictures (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - LSR Appraisals - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller (AAR) Estate - European and Asian Lamps and Candlesticks (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - LSR Appraisals - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller (AAR) Estate - Furniture (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - LSR Appraisals - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller (AAR) Estate - Screens, Carved Panels (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - LSR Appraisals - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller (AAR) Estate - Silver and Silk (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - LSR - Appraisals - James Robinson - Silver Collection, 1980 December 13 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - LSR - Estate - Auction - Christies' Proposal (Box 28, Folder 1)